import ins1 from "./ins1.mp4"
import ins2 from "./ins2.mp4"
import ins3 from "./ins3.mp4"
import ins4 from "./ins4.mp4"
import ins5 from "./ins5.mp4"
import ins6 from "./ins6.mp4"
import ins7 from "./ins7.mp4"
import ins8 from "./ins8.mp4"
import ins9 from "./ins9.mp4"
import ins10 from "./ins10.mp4"
import ins11 from "./ins11.mp4"
import ins12 from "./ins12.mp4"
import ins13 from "./ins13.mp4"
import ins14 from "./ins14.mp4"
import ins15 from "./ins15.mp4"
import ins16 from "./ins16.mp4"
import ins17 from "./ins17.mp4"
import ins18 from "./ins18.mp4"
import ins19 from "./ins19.mp4"
import ins20 from "./ins20.mp4"
import ins21 from "./ins21.mp4"
import ins22 from "./ins22.mp4"
import ins23 from "./ins23.mp4"
import ins24 from "./ins24.mp4"
import ins25 from "./ins25.mp4"
import ins26 from "./ins26.mp4"
import ins27 from "./ins27.mp4"
import ins28 from "./ins28.mp4"
import ins29 from "./ins29.mp4"
import ins30 from "./ins30.mp4"
import ins31 from "./ins31.mp4"
import ins32 from "./ins32.mp4"
import ins33 from "./ins33.mp4"
import ins34 from "./ins34.mp4"
import ins35 from "./ins35.mp4"
import ins36 from "./ins36.mp4"
import ins37 from "./ins37.mp4"
import ins38 from "./ins38.mp4"
import ins39 from "./ins39.mp4"
import ins40 from "./ins40.mp4"
import ins41 from "./ins41.mp4"
import ins42 from "./ins42.mp4"
import ins43 from "./ins43.mp4"
import ins44 from "./ins44.mp4"
import ins45 from "./ins45.mp4"
import ins46 from "./ins46.mp4"
import ins47 from "./ins47.mp4"
import ins48 from "./ins48.mp4"
import ins49 from "./ins49.mp4"
import ins50 from "./ins50.mp4"
import ins51 from "./ins51.mp4"
import ins52 from "./ins52.mp4"
import ins53 from "./ins53.mp4"
import ins54 from "./ins54.mp4"
import ins55 from "./ins55.mp4"
import ins56 from "./ins56.mp4"
import ins57 from "./ins57.mp4"
import ins58 from "./ins58.mp4"
import ins59 from "./ins59.mp4"
import ins60 from "./ins60.mp4"
import ins61 from "./ins61.mp4"
import ins62 from "./ins62.mp4"
import ins63 from "./ins63.mp4"
import ins64 from "./ins64.mp4"
import ins65 from "./ins65.mp4"
import ins66 from "./ins66.mp4"
import ins67 from "./ins67.mp4"
import ins68 from "./ins68.mp4"
import ins69 from "./ins69.mp4"
import ins70 from "./ins70.mp4"
import ins71 from "./ins71.mp4"
import ins72 from "./ins72.mp4"
import ins73 from "./ins73.mp4"
import ins74 from "./ins74.mp4"
import ins75 from "./ins75.mp4"
import ins76 from "./ins76.mp4"
import ins77 from "./ins77.mp4"
import ins78 from "./ins78.mp4"
import ins79 from "./ins79.mp4"
import ins80 from "./ins80.mp4"
import ins81 from "./ins81.mp4"
import ins82 from "./ins82.mp4"
import ins83 from "./ins83.mp4"
import ins84 from "./ins84.mp4"



export const instantFamly = [
    
    {
        id: 1035,
        videoFile: ins84,
        rusQuestion: "колышек",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a small stick or hook that sticks out from a surface and from which objects, especially clothes, can hang: ",
        answer: "peg",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1034,
        videoFile: ins83,
        rusQuestion: "добросовестный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "putting a lot of effort into your work: ",
        answer: "conscientious",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1033,
        videoFile: ins82,
        rusQuestion: "несосредоточенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "nervous or confused because you are worried about something:",
        answer: "distracted",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1032,
        videoFile: ins81,
        rusQuestion: "шов",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a piece of thread sewn in cloth, or the single movement of a needle and thread into and out of the cloth that produces this: ",
        answer: "stitch",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1031,
        videoFile: ins80,
        rusQuestion: "гипсовая повязка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "If a part of your body is in a cast, it has a plaster cast around it to protect it while a broken bone repairs itself: ",
        answer: "plaster cast",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1030,
        videoFile: ins79,
        rusQuestion: "каталка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a light bed on wheels, used to move patients in a hospital",
        answer: "gurney",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1029,
        videoFile: ins78,
        rusQuestion: "вспомнишь говно вот и оно",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "used in speech to say that someone one has been talking about has unexpectedly appeared",
        answer: "speak of the devil",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1028,
        videoFile: ins77,
        rusQuestion: "планка , дощечка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a thin, narrow piece of wood, plastic, or metal used to make floors, furniture, window coverings, etc.:",
        answer: "slat",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1027,
        videoFile: ins76,
        rusQuestion: "струя",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(to force a liquid) to flow out through a narrow opening in a fast stream: ",
        answer: "squirt",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1026,
        videoFile: ins75,
        rusQuestion: "святой",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(the title given to) a person who has received an official honour from the Christian, especially the Roman Catholic, Church for having lived in a good and holy way. The names of saints are sometimes used to name places and buildings: ",
        answer: "saint",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1025,
        videoFile: ins74,
        rusQuestion: "ребенок, начинающий ходить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a young child, especially one who is learning or has recently learned to walk",
        answer: "toddler",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1024,
        videoFile: ins73,
        rusQuestion: "стринги",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a piece of underwear or the bottom part of a bikini with a very narrow part at the back that does not cover the bottom",
        answer: "thong",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1023,
        videoFile: ins72,
        rusQuestion: "сравнительно",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "as compared to something else: ",
        answer: "comparatively",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1022,
        videoFile: ins71,
        rusQuestion: "составной",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a very large cinema building that has a lot of separate cinemas inside it",
        answer: "multiplex",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1021,
        videoFile: ins70,
        rusQuestion: "крэк-дом",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a house or flat where people use, sell, or buy crack (= an illegal drug)",
        answer: "crack house",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1020,
        videoFile: ins69,
        rusQuestion: "заземленный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "A child or young person who is ooooo is not allowed to go out as a punishment: ",
        answer: "grounded",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1019,
        videoFile: ins68,
        rusQuestion: "расстроенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "feeling annoyed or less confident because you cannot achieve what you want: ",
        answer: "frustrated",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1018,
        videoFile: ins67,
        rusQuestion: "работа по дому",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a job or piece of work that is often boring or unpleasant but needs to be done regularly: ",
        answer: "chore",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1017,
        videoFile: ins66,
        rusQuestion: "находка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "something good that happens unexpectedly, especially at a time when it is needed: ",
        answer: "godsend",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1016,
        videoFile: ins65,
        rusQuestion: "Боже упаси",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a way of saying that you hope something does not happen:",
        answer: "god forbid",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1015,
        videoFile: ins64,
        rusQuestion: "времяпрепровождение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an activity that is done for enjoyment: ",
        answer: "pastime",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1014,
        videoFile: ins63,
        rusQuestion: "артистичный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "being or wishing to seem very interested in everything connected with art and artists: ",
        answer: "arty",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1013,
        videoFile: ins62,
        rusQuestion: "обезвоженный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "not having the normal amount of water in your body so that you feel ill or weak",
        answer: "dehydrated",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1012,
        videoFile: ins61,
        rusQuestion: "ты сдался?",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to agree to something that you would not agree to before, after someone has persuaded you or threatened you: ",
        answer: "to cave",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1011,
        videoFile: ins60,
        rusQuestion: "манчкин",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "one of the small people with very high voices who are characters in the book and film .The Wizard of Oz. : ",
        answer: "munchkin",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1010,
        videoFile: ins59,
        rusQuestion: "награда",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "money paid as a reward: ",
        answer: "bounty",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1009,
        videoFile: ins58,
        rusQuestion: "картон",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "material like very thick, stiff paper, usually pale brown in colour, used especially for making boxes: ",
        answer: "cardboard",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1008,
        videoFile: ins57,
        rusQuestion: "черта",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a particular characteristic that can produce a particular type of behaviour: ",
        answer: "trait",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1007,
        videoFile: ins56,
        rusQuestion: "колея",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a deep, narrow mark made in soft ground especially by a wheel",
        answer: "rut",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1006,
        videoFile: ins55,
        rusQuestion: "явный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "clear and exact:",
        answer: "explicit",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1005,
        videoFile: ins54,
        rusQuestion: "блошиный рынок",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an event in a public place where people sell or exchange their unwanted possessions",
        answer: "swap meet",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1004,
        videoFile: ins53,
        rusQuestion: "злоба",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to intentionally annoy, upset, or hurt someone: ",
        answer: "spite",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1003,
        videoFile: ins52,
        rusQuestion: "непристойный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(of behaviour, speech, dress, etc.) sexual in an obvious and rude way: ",
        answer: "lewd",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1002,
        videoFile: ins51,
        rusQuestion: "поврежденные товары",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "products that are broken, cracked, scratched, etc.",
        answer: "damaged goods",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1001,
        videoFile: ins50,
        rusQuestion: "ярость",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(a period of) extreme or violent anger: ",
        answer: "rage",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 1000,
        videoFile: ins49,
        rusQuestion: "осторожный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "Someone who is cautious avoids risks:",
        answer: "cautious",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 999,
        videoFile: ins48,
        rusQuestion: "бросать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to throw something carelessly: ",
        answer: "toss",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 998,
        videoFile: ins47,
        rusQuestion: "врожденный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an inbred quality or characteristic is firmly established in a person: ",
        answer: "inbred",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 997,
        videoFile: ins46,
        rusQuestion: "цвести",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "When a tree or plant blossoms, it produces flowers before producing fruit that can be eaten: ",
        answer: "blossom",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 996,
        videoFile: ins45,
        rusQuestion: "дебошир",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "noisy and possibly violent: ",
        answer: "rowdy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 995,
        videoFile: ins44,
        rusQuestion: "сахарная шуба",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make something seem more positive or pleasant than it really is: ",
        answer: "sugarcoat",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 994,
        videoFile: ins43,
        rusQuestion: "воссоединение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an occasion when a country that was temporarily divided into smaller countries is joined together again as one country: ",
        answer: "reunification",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 993,
        videoFile: ins42,
        rusQuestion: "смешиваться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to mix or combine, or be mixed or combined:",
        answer: "mingle",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 992,
        videoFile: ins41,
        rusQuestion: "оснащенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "having the necessary tools, clothes, equipment, etc.: ",
        answer: "equipped",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 991,
        videoFile: ins40,
        rusQuestion: "косичка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a length of hair that is tied at the back of the head or at each side of the head, sometimes in a plait (= twist): ",
        answer: "pigtail",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 990,
        videoFile: ins39,
        rusQuestion: "эмбриональный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "relating to a fetus (= a young human being or animal before birth): ",
        answer: "fetal",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 989,
        videoFile: ins38,
        rusQuestion: "скорбящий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "feeling very sad because someone has died: ",
        answer: "grieving",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 988,
        videoFile: ins37,
        rusQuestion: "перемещенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "having been forced to leave your home, for example by a war or dangerous event: ",
        answer: "displaced",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 987,
        videoFile: ins36,
        rusQuestion: "защитник",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to publicly support or suggest an idea, development, or way of doing something: ",
        answer: "advocate",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 986,
        videoFile: ins35,
        rusQuestion: "опрокидываться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to (cause to) fall over onto one side: ",
        answer: "tip over",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 985,
        videoFile: ins34,
        rusQuestion: "плюшевый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "soft to touch: ",
        answer: "plush",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 984,
        videoFile: ins33,
        rusQuestion: "изменяющий жизнь",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "having an effect that is strong enough to change someone's life: ",
        answer: "life-altering",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 983,
        videoFile: ins32,
        rusQuestion: "накачанный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "excited about something that is going to happen: ",
        answer: "pumped",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 982,
        videoFile: ins31,
        rusQuestion: "столешница",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a counter in a kitchen",
        answer: "countertop",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 981,
        videoFile: ins30,
        rusQuestion: "ветхость",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the state of being broken or old and needing to be repaired:",
        answer: "disrepair",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 980,
        videoFile: ins29,
        rusQuestion: "мешок с обедом",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a bag lunch ",
        answer: "sack lunch",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 979,
        videoFile: ins28,
        rusQuestion: "заключать в тюрьму",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to put or keep someone in prison or in a place used as a prison: ",
        answer: "incarcerate",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 978,
        videoFile: ins27,
        rusQuestion: "размещение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a temporary position or job in an organization: ",
        answer: "placement",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 977,
        videoFile: ins26,
        rusQuestion: "прыгать от места к месту",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to increase and decrease in level many times, so that it may be hard to say what is going to happen: ",
        answer: "bounce around",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 976,
        videoFile: ins25,
        rusQuestion: "мет",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "methamphetamine",
        answer: "meth",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 975,
        videoFile: ins24,
        rusQuestion: "клеймо",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a strong lack of respect for a person or a group of people or a bad opinion of them because they have done something society does not approve of: ",
        answer: "stigma",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 974,
        videoFile: ins23,
        rusQuestion: "сюжет",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the story of a book, film, play, etc.: ",
        answer: "plot",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 973,
        videoFile: ins22,
        rusQuestion: "подросток",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "teenage",
        answer: "teen",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 972,
        videoFile: ins21,
        rusQuestion: "этническая принадлежность",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a large group of people with a shared culture, language, history, set of traditions, etc., or the fact of belonging to one of these groups: ",
        answer: "ethnicity",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 971,
        videoFile: ins20,
        rusQuestion: "зачать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to become pregnant, or to cause a baby to begin to form: ",
        answer: "conceive",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 970,
        videoFile: ins19,
        rusQuestion: "стойкость",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "courage and determination despite difficulty: ",
        answer: "grit",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 969,
        videoFile: ins18,
        rusQuestion: "напряжение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a force or influence that stretches, pulls, or puts pressure on something, sometimes causing damage: ",
        answer: "strain",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 968,
        videoFile: ins17,
        rusQuestion: "томиться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to exist in an unpleasant or unwanted situation, often for a long time: ",
        answer: "languish",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 967,
        videoFile: ins16,
        rusQuestion: "мрачный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "If a situation is oooo, there is little or no hope for the future: ",
        answer: "bleak",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 966,
        videoFile: ins15,
        rusQuestion: "перегружен",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "having or supplied with too much of something: ",
        answer: "overloaded",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 965,
        videoFile: ins14,
        rusQuestion: "заполнить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to become full, or to make something become full: ",
        answer: "fill up",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 964,
        videoFile: ins13,
        rusQuestion: "экспромтом",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "without looking for information and without thinking carefully; immediately: ",
        answer: "offhand",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 963,
        videoFile: ins12,
        rusQuestion: "взрыв",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an explosion: ",
        answer: "blast",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 962,
        videoFile: ins11,
        rusQuestion: "приемная семья",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the care of a child, usually for a limited time, by someone who is not the child's legal parent:",
        answer: "foster care",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 961,
        videoFile: ins10,
        rusQuestion: "полотенце",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a piece of cloth or paper used for drying someone or something that is wet: ",
        answer: "towel",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 960,
        videoFile: ins9,
        rusQuestion: "кожаный салон",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: " an inside made of animal skin",
        answer: "leather interior",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 959,
        videoFile: ins8,
        rusQuestion: "включать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to contain something as a part of something else, or to make something part of something else: ",
        answer: "include",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 958,
        videoFile: ins7,
        rusQuestion: "экстракорпоральное оплодотворение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a treatment for a woman who cannot become pregnant naturally, in which an egg is fertilized outside her body and the resulting embryo is put into her womb to develop into a baby",
        answer: "in vitro fertilization",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 957,
        videoFile: ins6,
        rusQuestion: "выкашливать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to produce or give something unwillingly, esp. money: ",
        answer: "cough up",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 956,
        videoFile: ins5,
        rusQuestion: "витраж",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "glass that has been coloured and cut into various shapes to form pictures or patterns, used especially in church windows: ",
        answer: "stained glass",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 955,
        videoFile: ins4,
        rusQuestion: "Французские двери",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a pair of glass doors, usually opening from the back of a house into its garden",
        answer: "french doors",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 954,
        videoFile: ins3,
        rusQuestion: "моча",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "urine: ",
        answer: "piss",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 953,
        videoFile: ins2,
        rusQuestion: "сальто",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to buy something, such as a house, that is not in very good condition, improve it, then sell it quickly for more money:",
        answer: "flip",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 952,
        videoFile: ins1,
        rusQuestion: "встроенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "If a place or piece of equipment has built-in objects, they are permanently connected and cannot be easily removed: ",
        answer: "built-in",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
];